(Penny:)And I wanted to make you feel better,
(Penny:)so I planned something
very special for you.
(Leonard:)I can already feel it working.
(Mrs Hofstadter(on webcam):)Hello, Leonard.
Mom?!
(Mrs Hofstadter:)I understand you have been whining
about my parenting
(Mrs Hofstadter:)in order to emotionally manipulate
your girlfriend.
I... uh...
(Penny:)Bernadette told me everything.
(Penny:)Now you don't get the left
or the right.
Lets discuss why you continue
to involve me in your sex life.
(Leonard:)Oh, please, Mommy.
No, Mommy.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)When you were six years old,
(Mrs Hofstadter:)you walked in on me
and your father naked.
(Mrs Hofstadter:)I was swatting his bottom with
your brand-new Ping-Pong paddle.
(Leonard:)I didn't dream that?
(Mrs Hofstadter:)How did that make you feel?
Penny, come back!
I'm sad for real now!